# Karin Ljunggren

Frontend developer, Gothenburg



I love creating delightful and functional web solutions.

Strong focus on the user and I master various frontend skills from design to coding to make an optimal web experience..

I prefer working with React.js, Next.js, Vue.js, Headless CMS, but also WordPress custom themes.

Passionate also about UX/ UI and Accessibility.

# **Work Experience**

## Boozang Technologies INC - Frontend developer

2017 - current - part time, project based

Boozang SaaS, based in Montreal, is a tool that tests your web application flows end-to-end, using a low-code approach.

I have contributed to multiple projects, focusing on enhancing user experience and functionality. In each project, my work was centered on creating seamless, high-performance user interfaces, utilizing technologies like React.js, Vue.js, WordPress and SCSS/LESS.

- Designed and developed Boozang's homepage, improving user engagement.
- Refactored the admin interface of a legacy app for better usability.
- Led frontend refactoring of Boozang Management for enhanced accessibility.
- Developed TheLab, a training platform for the Boozang tool.
- Improved UX of the Boozang test tool to streamline user interactions.

## Kungälvs kommun - Hourly temp caregiver

Dec 2022 - current

Caregiver for older people and assistant for persons with disabilities. Adapting to varying needs allows me to contribute to improving clients' comfort and independence. Interim employment.

## Knowit connectivity - Frontend developer

June 2021 - Dec 2021

Consultant as Frontend developer in Gothenburg. Implemented responsive, user-friendly admin interfaces using Vue.js and Vuetify, Vuex and SCSS.

## Contact

kaljunggren@gmail.com
Tel: 0768 - 514619
GitHub
LinkedIn
Online Portfolio

#### Skills

- Javascript/ES6,
   TypeScript, jQuery,
   React.js, Next.js, Vue.js,
   Vuex
- WordPress, Headless CMS
- SCSS/LESS, Styled-components
- Figma, User Centered Design, User testing
- Accessibility-WCAG
- Communication and Collaboration
- Adaptability and Continuous Learning

## Tools

- Git
- Agile development
- Jira, Azure DevOps

## **Education**

#### Medieinstitutet

- UX and Accessibility
   Oct Dec 2024
- TypeScript
   March May 2024

## **IT-Högskolan**

- Web development -React.js
   Jan - March 2024
- UX and User Centered Design Oct - Dec 2023

#### **Linnaeus University**

Web Development, 7.5hp. Aug 2016 - Nov 2016

## Hogia group - HR Products — Frontend developer

Jan 2019 - July 2020

As part of a team I was responsible for building and optimizing high-performance admin web tools for Human Resources, utilizing technologies like JavaScript/TupeScript, Aurelia.js and SCSS/LESS.

# JGL Digital agency - Web Developer

April 2018 - September 2018

WordPress and WooCommerce projects. Developed custom responsive WordPress and WooCommerce themes. Customized and optimized frontend components to improve performance and user experience utilizing PHP, jQuery and SCSS.

# Folkuniversitetet, Kungälv - Italian Teacher

2006 - 2013

Teaching Italian. Beginner to advanced. Evening courses.

## Medborgarskolan, Kungälv - Italian Teacher

2005 - 2012

Teaching Italian. Beginner to advanced. Evening courses.

I excluded prior jobs or education that may not be relevant.

## **University West**

Web Development, 45hp Aug 2015 - June 2016

#### **Linnaeus University**

Web Development, 15 hp. Jan 2015 - June 2015

#### **GrVux**

Studies on systems and network technologies, undergraduate level, 40 weeks. Jan 2014 - Nov 2014

# **University of Gothenburg**

Degree of Bachelor of Arts in modern languages. Studies of the Italian and Spanish language, literature and culture. Main subject: Italian. Studies in Sweden and Italy. Final exams in January 2012

#### Volunteer work

Cat shelter volunteer for 10 years

# Languages

Swedish (native)
English (fluent)
Italian (fluent)
Spanish (proficient)